(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T16:59:39.400957",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
揺れる街灯 穂雨降る感情
The trembling street lights, the pelting rain
感覚のテレパス
and an emotional telepath.
迷子のふたりはコンタクト
The lost two made contact,
ココロは恋を知りました
and my heart learned of love.
タイトロープ ツジハギの制服
Tightrope, a uniform of stitched creation,
重力のディスコミュニケーション
a gravitational discommunication.
眼光 赤色にキラキラ
Glint of red, flashing bright,
ナニカが起きる胸騒ぎ
something's coming: an endless sense of dread.
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, yes I'm an alien,
あなたの心を惑わせる
I lead your defenseless heart astray.
交ざりあう宇宙の引力で
Within the melding gravity of the milky way,
感じてる気持ちはトキメキ
deeply I can feel those feelings beating.
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, that's right, I'm your alien,
引きあう心は逃れられない
your heart strings pulled and deftly lulled.
あなたに未体験あげる
Here, have an un-experience,
異世界の果てまで トキメキ スキ
so your heart can blast off to another world!
点灯と消灯を繰り返している蛍光灯
Fluorescent lights that repeatedly turn on and off,
超常な混沌が静かにあなたを蝕んだ
a supernatural chaos has quietly eaten away at you.
並行な信号は特異点に因り交わった
Parallel signals intersected due to singularity,
創造現実盲信症 感応性本能
creative reality, blind faith, sensitive instinct.
シンドローム ひとりきり夜な夜な
Syndrome, all alone at night,
空想描くまるですグリモワ
imagining, it's like a grimoire.
サーチライト避ける浮遊機
Searchlight avoiding floating machine,
「まだあなたは全てを知りたい？」
"Do you still want to know everything?"
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, yes I'm an alien,
あなたの心を惑わせる
I lead your defenseless heart astray.
瞳に映らない引力に気づいてよわたしは―
Please notice the gravitational force not in my eyes—
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, that's right I'm your alien,
触れあえば傷は二度と消えない
if we touch each other, wounds never disappear.
降りそそぐ無数の隕石もときめく心には届かない!
Countless meteorites raining down won't reach your heart!
エイリアン ふたりはエイリアン
Alien, we are aliens,
高鳴る気持ちが抑えられない!
I can't control my excitement!
あなたは未確認生命体
You are an unidentified life form,
異世界の果てまであなたが好き
I love you to the end of another world.
点灯と消灯を繰り返している蛍光灯
Fluorescent lights that repeatedly turn on and off
ゆれる街灯 蔦伏せる雨
The trembling street lights, the pelting rain
振れる感情 感覚のテレパス
Warmth excites an emotional telepath
迷子のふたりはコンタクト
In the night, the lost two finally made contact
ココロは恋を知りました
My heart learned of the human concept known as love
タイトロープ ツジハギの制服
T-t-t-tight rope, a uniform of stitched creation
重度のディスコミュニケーション
It provokes a discommunication
眼光赤色にキラキラ
Glint of hope? No, actually just a flashing of red
ナニカが起きる胸騒ぎ
Something’s coming: I’ve got this endless sense of dread
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, yes I’m an alien
あなたの心を惑わせる
I come in peace but lead your defenseless heart astray
交ざりあう宇宙の引力で 感じてる気持ちはドキメキ
Within the melding gravity of the milky way...
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, that’s right, I’m your alien
引き合う心は逃れられない
Your heart strings pulled and deftly lulled
あなたに未体験あげる
Here, have an un-experience
異世界の果てまで ドキメキ スキ
So your heart can blast off to another planet
点灯と消灯を繰り返している蛍光灯
Fluorescent lights that repeatedly turn on and off
超常な混沌が静かにあなたを蝕んだ
A supernatural chaos has quietly eaten away at you
並行な信号は特異点に因み交わった
Parallel signals intersected due to singularity
創造現実盲信症 感応性本能
Creative reality blind faith sensitive instinct
シンドローム ひとりきり夜な夜な
Syndrome, all alone at night behind bars
空想 描くまるでグリモワール
Imagining, it's like a grimoire
サーチライト 避ける遊撃機
Searchlight avoid floating machine
「まだあなたはすべてを知りたい?」
“Do you still want to know everything?”
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, yes I’m an alien
あなたの心を惑わせる
I come in peace but lead your defenseless heart astray
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, that’s right I’m your alien
触れあえば傷は二度と消えない
If we touch each other, the wounds will never disappear again
降りそそぐ無数の隕石も
Countless meteorites raining down
ときめく心には 届かない!
I can't reach your excited heart!
エイリアン ふたりはエイリアン
Alien, we are aliens
高鳴る気持ちが抑えられない!
I can't control my excitement!
あなたは未確認生命体
You are an unidentified life form
異世界の果てまで あなたが 好き
I love you to the end of another world
3D！はー！
3D! Ha!
やばりゃー！
Oh no!
あ、カメラこっち！
Ah, the camera's over here!
はーい！に、おなかやんね、さつやんね、オッケーやんね。
Yeah! Two, stomach right, photo right, okay right.
3Dもいい、もう、いい、いい。大丈夫？
3D is good, already, good, good. Are you okay?
はあー！
Haah!
やばりゃー！
Oh no!
はあー！やっぱりゃー！
Haah! Oh no!
はーう！ブリジ！ブリジかやんね、オッケー！
Haau! Bridge! Bridge right, okay!
はーい！いらっしゃい！エアニオ十五3D！
Hiii! Welcome to Airani Iofteen 3D!
Jangan lupa di apa, di-tweet ya. Airani Iofteen 15 pakai I.
Don't forget to, what, tweet it ya. Airani Iofteen 15 with an I.
Kita udah 2 tahun masih ada yang pakai L. Jadi lovibe. So is Airani Iofteen with I, not L. We're already been through this for two years, okay? Okay?
It's been two years and some people still use an L. So lovibe. So it's Airani Iofteen with I, not L. We've already been through this for two years, okay? Okay?
Naaaah! Halo, coba dilihat loh komentarnya.
Naaaah! Hello, try looking at the comments.
Hai! Hai! Airani Iofteen special day, so I really want to make this something really special.
Hi! Hi! Airani Iofteen special day, so I really want to make this something really special.
So please don't forget to tweet. Tolong, onegai ne. Koko da yo! Oke.
So please don't forget to tweet. Please, onegai ne. Right here! Okay.
Oke, kita mulai, bismillah. Halo, salam kenal. Ioforia, oibisho! Pagi... eh bukan pagi sih, malam. Malam, aku Airani Iofteen atau Yopi atau Yofie dari Hololive Indonesia generasi pertama.
Okay, let's start, bismillah. Hello, nice to meet you. Ioforia, oibisho! Morning... eh not morning, evening. Evening, I'm Airani Iofteen or Yopi or Yofie from Hololive Indonesia 1st Generation.
Ikki-sen no Iofide Indonesianoko... Arigatou gozaimasu!
Hai! Haaa... Tte iu koto de ne.
Hi! Haaa... So with that being said.
ようこそ！ようこそ！
Welcome! Welcome!
見てみて、見てみて、見てみて！ありがとーう、見えとーう、見やすーう！
Look, look, look! Thank you, can see, looks easy!
Itu sini bisa lihat. Oh, adaね。
You can see over here. Oh, there is.
So I'm actually, if you don't forget, I'm a princess. You can get it. Look at that. That is my home, actually.
So ya, jangan salah ya. Yofi no... iya, itu rumah Yofi. Da, moratorium enggak tahu, enggak tahu, tahu enggak, tahu enggak? Mau liat enggak?
So yeah, don't get it wrong. Yofi's... yeah, that's Yofi's house. Moratorium, don't know, don't know, do you know, do you know? Want to see?
Oke, ada UFO! Yofino... UFO! Doko do?
Okay, there's a UFO! Yofi's... UFO! Where?
このUFOの、Yopi！No? Do? かわいい、かわいいしょ？ルチュかん？kayak Yopi. Lucu. Hai!
This is Yofi's UFO! No? Do? Cute, cute right? Looks like Yofi. Cute. Hi!
Betul, ada yang mau request pose enggak? Pose request, ada? Is there any pose request?
Right, is there anyone who wants to request a pose? Pose request, is there? Is there any pose request?
これな、なぽぽこ、 kalian ngetik juga kelihatan sama Yopi, apa?
Even when you guys type, Yopi can see it too, what?
あ、Yofi tau, Yofi tahu this. Uh? Uh? Apa?
Ah, Yofi knows, Yofi knows this. Uh? Uh? What?
あ、あ！あっ！OK, OK, OK.
Ah, ah! Ahh! Okay, okay, okay.
Hai, T pose! まあ、今さらT pose.
Hi, T pose! Well, T pose now of all times.
はい。T pose, T pose, stand and then...
Hi. T pose, T pose, stand and then...
Jojo... Jojo? Oh, yang Hanco-ku no.
Jojo... Jojo? Oh, the Hanco-ku one.
われわわ... yabe, doshiyo. Dekinai!
Owarawa wa... yabe, what should I do. Can't do it!
われわは... can't do it. T-pose, kayanya udah. Anything else? Nengaru? Jojo to, ano, bridge, igai no aru?
Owarawa wa... can't do it. T-pose, I think that's it. Anything else? Nengaru? Jojo and, um, bridge, anything else?
ある？ある？
Are there any? Are there any?
ここはどこ？
Where is this?
もういいか。
Oh well.
ここで次の場所行く？
Shall we go to the next place from here?
行く？みたい？見てみたい？
Go? Want to see? Want to see it?
じゃあもう一個じゃ。指笛したらもう一個。
Then one more. When I whistle, one more.
オッケー、見る？見る？オッケー、Let's go to the next place!
Okay, want to see? Okay, let's go to the next place!
スーウ！うわ！
Suu! Whoa!
お？え？どこ？
Oh? Eh? Where?
あれ？え？
Huh? Eh?
エリナの話？
Elina's story?
おいコラ！
Hey, you!
スー！
Suu!
Come down. Come here. Here. Here. Here.
あ、ワープ！スー！
Ah, warp! Suu!
スー！
Suu!
ああ、いいこ、いいこ。こっち。いいこ。いいこ、こっち。
Ah, good boy. Over here. Good boy. Over here.
どこ？ここ分かるし？
Where? Do you know this place?
おい！
Hey!
違う！
No! That's wrong!
違う、違う、違う、ここ。
No, no, no, over here.
Here, here, here, here boy, here boy, here boy.
スー！
Suu!
真ん中！真ん中！真ん中！
Center! Center! Center!
スー！真ん中、真ん中、真ん中にしに。
Suu! Center, center, right in the center.
から！
From there!
スー！
Suu!
こっち！
This way!
もう、まじ。こっち。
Seriously. Over here.
うん、だ。
Yeah, right.
さあ、そこかよ！
Oh come on, right there?!
スー！うっせえ！うっせえ！うるせえ！
Suu! Shut up! Shut up! So noisy!
ここ！
Here!
スー！
Suu!
ああ、here boy, here boy.
Ah, here boy, here boy.
ああ、来るか？来るか？来るか？来るか？
Ah, coming? Coming? Coming? Coming?
スー！
Suu!
まいっか！
Whatever!
もう、意味分かんなくしらない！
I don't get it anymore! I don't care!
いまさら！
Now of all times!
Boya! Boy! Boy! Boy!
あ！
Ah!
さかな～
Sakana~
ちやなの～
Chiya-no~
ハロー！こともまたぎで、Yopi。ハーイ！
Hello! Back again with Yopi. Hi!
じゃあ、これ、き... This is my atelier, this is my studio. Crystal room, ya?
So this... This is my atelier, this is my studio. Crystal room, ya?
Bukan gudang. Tapi ya si Yopi...
It's not a warehouse. But yeah, Yopi...
Yopi itu turu, Yopi itu turu di sini, tapi enggak mandi di sini sih, tidur di sini, makan di sini, iya.
Yopi sleeps here, but she doesn't bathe here, she sleeps here, eats here, yeah.
Tapi ya kita mau lihat ya. This by the way ya, yang kalian lihat di belakang,
But yeah, let's take a look. This by the way, what you see in the back,
ini adalah yang dipakai di MV High Five. Kalian inget enggak waktu stage-nya... anu, High Five-nya, lagu yang... eeee, detektif...
is what was used in the High Five MV. Do you remember when the stage... um, High Five, the song where... um, detective...
yang anu, ini... kan? Kok. Can you see it? Can you see it? So this is...
um, this... right? Look. Can you see it? Can you see it? So this is...
So this is actually the first drawing I made for Yyshu for her 100k? 100k? 100k? Yeah. 100,000 subscriber-nya, yang Yypi bikin buat Yyshu 100.000 subs.
So this is actually the first drawing I made for Yisu for her 100k? 100k? 100k? Yeah. 100,000 subscribers, that Yipi made for Yisu's 100k subs.
Nah, ini lagi. Kecil-kecil. Nah, ini adalah remastered version dari pertama kali Yypi, apa sih? Gambar pertama pas debutnya. Ini debut-nya Sako-no... awal-nya... eh, kana? Anu, moto SD version-nya.
Now, here's another one. Smaller. Now, this is a remastered version of the very first time Yipi, what was it? The first drawing when she debuted. This was Sako-no's debut... the beginning... eh, kana? Um, the former SD version.
Dan, masih ada kah? Ada?
And, is there still more? Is there?
Koko, koko, kotchi, kotchi kuru? Taran! Mama, mi teru? Mama, mi teru?
Here, here, coming this way? Tada! Mama, are you watching? Mama, are you watching?
Ini ya, anu... tahun-nya mama, birthday-nya, buat... ini buat ulang tahunnya mama. Tete... Tete...
This is, um... mama's year, her birthday, for... this is for mama's birthday. Te-te... Te-te...
Sendiri, ngakak, tete... Arigatou! Hahaha.
By myself, laughing, te-te... Arigatou! Hahaha.
Aduuh, capek. Capek, lucu kan, lucu kan, lucu kan. Oke. Nah, tapi kan kita udah di studio nih.
Oof, I'm tired. Tired, it's funny right, funny right, funny right. Okay. Now, we're already in the studio.
Nah, studio ini dekat rasanya.
Well, this studio feels close.
Oekaki shitaku nai? Do you want to draw something well in this studio, I think. Right, right?
Don't you want to draw? Do you want to draw something well in this studio, I think. Right, right?
Yes, guys. Sebentar ya, Yypi cari sesuatu untuk buat gambar.
Yes, guys. Wait a minute, Yipi is looking for something to draw with.
Okey, sagasu...
Okay, looking...
eh, okaki, oekaki, oekaki. Oh, okaki!
uh, drawing, drawing, drawing. Oh, drawing tool!
Uwooo! Ada! Ada, guys, ada, guys!
Whoa! There is! There is, guys, there is, guys!
Ini siapa sih yang simpan di atas? Emjang, tak setinggi!
Who on earth put this up top? Man, it's too high!
This is too high for me.
Ah, gimana sih? Ah... Thanks!
Ah, how do I reach? Ah... Thanks!
Ah, itu, tapi, tapi, Yopi, Yopi, Yopi, pas, bersih, Yopi, ah, pas, oh, bersih. Udah.
Ah, that, but, but Yopi, Yopi, Yopi, just right, clean, Yopi, ah, just right, oh, clean. Done.
Eh, jangan, pendek-pendek. Apaan? Ya, bentar, not too short. Okay.
Eh, don't, too short. What's this? Wait, not too short. Okay.
Heh, okay. Yopi, yopi, sa? Si, na?
Heh! Ah, ah, udah. Okay.
Heh! Ah, ah, done. Okay.
Yossha!
Yosh!
Hahaha! Bersih dong. Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hahaha! So clean. Hi! Hi! Hi!
Gimana? Gede kan? Is this actually kind of a little bit too big for me? Oh guys.
How is it? It's big, right? Is this actually kind of a little bit too big for me? Oh guys.
Heh! Okay. Dulu, situ? Dulu, situ? Kayaknya sih, ya.
Heh! Okay. Over there? Over there? I guess so, yeah.
Nah, kaya, kayaknya hari ini, nih, dengan, dengan, mau, nge-gambar, gitu, mau, rasa.
Well, so, like today, you know, with, with, wanting to draw, like that, feeling it.
Jadi, Yopi, ini, mau, ng-gambar, pakai, ini. Jeng, jeng! Jeng, jeng! Ini udah, ada. Wiiy!
So, Yopi, here, wants to draw, using, this. Ta-da! Ta-da! It's here already. Whew!
Pendek, bukan pendek, ininya, kegedean. Mu, ya, fi-ga, kecil, okay, dan, emon, ini, yang, kegedean, ya?
Short, not short, this is too big. Mu, yeah, fi-ga, small, okay, and, emon, this, which is too big, right?
Okay. Nah, sekarang, osi, osi, osi, osi. Oshi, diam.
Okay. Now, shh, shh, shh, shh. Shh, quiet.
Nah, karena, ini, gayanya, lu, dari, paint, paint. Ah, ketemunya, okay.
Well, because, this, the style, you, from, paint, paint. Ah, found it, okay.
Hah, nah, gimana? Ah, waaah!
Huh, well, how is it? Ah, waaah!
Ih, da, da, da, da, da. Aaah! Eh? Eh?
Eh? Ah, gimana? Mau, nih, kok, lucu? Masak, masak, lucu, sih?
Eh? Ah, how? What's this, why is it cute? Really, really, is it cute?
Eh? Eh? Tapi, kamu, yang, di-sana, kok, kamu, bersih? Ih, kok, kamu, bersih, sih? Nah, di-sana, ada, nih.
Eh? Eh? But you, the one over there, why are you clean? Ih, why are you clean? Well, over there, there is.
Kayak, ke-ce-da, nih? Gak, ya, ca-u? Gak, ya, pretty, ya? Don't you think?
Like, pretty, right? Don't you think?
You want to get, paint? You want to get, painted? Mau, ku-sa, gak, ya?
You want to get paint? You want to get painted? Want to get a brush, right?
Ah, ya, iko, ya, mu, mi-na, wa, mi-na-wa, ne, ku-ray! Hya! Tya! Tya! Tya! Woah!
Ah, yeah, let's go, everyone, everyone, hey, splash! Hya! Tya! Tya! Tya! Woah!
Hahahaha! Yaa, dan-kan, kayak, gitu, nih, dai. Gi-ma-na? Gi-ma-na? Gi-ma-na? Tu, nih, dai, ya, yopi? Gi-ma-na?
Hahaha! Yeah, second, like, that, nih, dai. How is it? How is it? How is it? That's, dai, right, Yopi? How is it?
Mm, mm, enak. Lagian lagi. Okay.
Mm, mm, nice. One more time. Okay.
Hah, ya, one, one, more, time? One, more, time? Yes, yes. Kyaaa! Kya!
Huh, yeah, one more time? One more time? Yes, yes. Kyaaa! Kya!
Igo? Ma-gi-ka? Ma-gi-ka? Okay, mau, satu, kali, ya, me-nan-ga, ini, yang, suka, dhu, ya? Ja, iko, ya?
Again? Again? Okay, want to do it one more time, because everyone likes this, right? So let's go, yeah?
Ja, ni, ku-ray! Tya! Tya! Tya! Wuaaah!
So, here, splash! Tya! Tya! Tya! Wuaaah!
Gi-ma-na, nih? Tu, nih, dai? Mm, tu, nih, dai? Okay, udah, deh.
How is this? That, right? Mm, that, right? Okay, done.
Tu, ya, ku, hon-ki-ri, hon-ki-ri, ga-ki, shi-mas-su! Tu, yopi, mau, nge-gam-bar, be-ne-ran.
So, yeah, I, really, really, will draw! So, Yopi, wants to draw, for real.
Ma-te, ne, ben-tar, gede. Ro-pe, ro-pe.
Wait, hey, a bit, big. Ro-pe, ro-pe.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm... Sene, ring. Sho, sho, sho...
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm... Over here, ring. Sho, sho, sho...
Ya, sho, sho. Iyo, ta-ri-an. Ro-pe, lab-lab. Da-ri-sho. Hai, ton, ton.
Yeah, sho, sho. Iyo, tari-an. Ro-pe, lab-lab. Da-ri-sho. Hai, ton, ton.
Oish-sho! Ah! Okay, okay. De-ka-ta! De-ka-ta, poi! De-ka-ta, poi! De-ka-ta, poi! De-ka-ta!
Oish-sho! Ah! Okay, okay. Done! Done, poi! Done, poi! Done, poi! Done!
Miru? Miru, miru, miru? Hmm, miru? Miru? Okay, ja. De-ka-ta! De-ka-ta? De-ka-ta?
Look? Look, look, look? Hmm, look? Look? Okay, then. Done! Done? Done?
Hahahaha! Miru, miru, shu! Ah, ah!
Hahaha! Look, look, shu! Ah, ah!
Hallo, ini Yophoria! Ro-pe, ro-pe. Hebat.
Hello, this is Yophoria! Ro-pe, ro-pe. Amazing.
Do, do, ka-wa-yo? Ka-wa-yo? El-jun-ga, el-jun-ga, el-jun-dong. Tapi, yang, gam-bar-nya, le-bih, lu-cu, ya, gak?
How, how, is it cute? Is it cute? El-junga, el-junga, el-jungdong. But, the drawing is cuter, right?
Heh! El-chu! El-chu! Uh, cute, cute, okay. Really, is it cute though?
Ka-wa-ii? Thank you! Haa, a-ri-ga-to!
Ca-pe-k, ya. Eh, pose, pose, screenshot, screenshot? Hmm?
Tired, huh. Eh, pose, pose, screenshot, screenshot? Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm? Hah. Hah. Siku, siku, siku, siku, siku... Eh, doro, kore, omoi, na? Ini, be-rat, loh, guys. Sebentar, guys, ya. Mau, sim-pan, du-lu.
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm? Hah. Hah. Siku, siku, siku, siku, siku... Eh, doro, kore, omoi, na? This is heavy, guys. Wait, guys, yeah. Let's store it first.
Hais-sho! Haa... Haa...
Haa... Haa... Ca-pe! Hahaha!
Haa... Haa... Tired! Hahaha!
Okay. Haa, mau, a-pa, ya? Mau, po-se, la-gi? Mmm? Mmm? Mau, a-pa? Mau, a-pa? Mau, i-ni? Ooh!
Okay. Haa, what do you want? Want another pose? Mmm? Mmm? What do you want? What do you want? Want this? Ooh!
A-re, ga, i-te! A-yu, po-se. Don-na, po-se? Po-se, po-se, po-se, po-se. Hallo, Yophoria! Hallo, Yophorian, do-ru? Hallo! Wel-com-to, K-K-C! Wel-com-to, Yophoria, fam-i-ly!
That's right, that pose! What pose? Pose, pose, pose, pose. Hello, Yophoria! Hello, Yophorians, doing? Hello! Welcome to K-K-C! Welcome to Yophoria family!
Hai! Mau, ma-po, la-gi?
Hi! Want another pose?
あーでもさ、この後ゲスト来るかもしれない。どうしよう？
"Ah, but you know, a guest might come after this. What should I do?"
ゲストある？よふぃってゲストある？ある？
"Are there guests? Does Yofi have guests? Are there?"
え、よふぃぶにゲストいる？え？ふにゃ。あ、ふにゃ。
"Wait, are there guests on Yofi's stream? Huh? Funya. Ah, funya."
え、ターンアウト、アイハブゲストドゥ！
"It turns out I have a guest though!"
え、ゲスト誰だな？あ、もっちもち！
"Uh, who could the guest be? Ah, mochi-mochi!"
はろ、ぱぎ？
"Hello, pagi?"
はろ？はろ？はろ？どなたですか？誰です？
"Hello? Hello? Hello? Who is this? Who is it?"
時のそらびーん！
"Tokino Sora-beeeam!"
あーー！よふぃのねさんです！
"Ahhh! It's Yofi's big sister!"
あーー！おめでとう！スリーディー！ありがとうーー！
"Ahhh! Congratulations on 3D! Thank you so much!"
ということで、ありがとうね、わざわざ来てくれて。
"So thank you so much for taking the time to come."
I love you! I love you!
I love you! はずかしい！ありがとうね、本当に来てくれてありがとう。
"I love you! So embarrassing! Thank you so much for really coming."
いやあ、とーりえ、かわいいね。
"Man, Torie is so cute."
本当？本当？よ、よ、よぴーの、かわいい、かわいい、かわいい、これ、やばい。
"Really? Really? Yopi's... so cute, cute, cute, this is crazy."
いや、そらちゃんはもう最高に可愛いから。
"Man, Sora-chan is super cute."
ありがとう！ということでね。似ちゃう？似ちゃう？
"Thank you! So yeah. Do we look alike?"
似合ってる？かわいい？ありがとうってね。
"Does it suit me? Cute? Thank you, you know."
せっかくおねえさんが来てくれたからね、ちょっとねゲームしたいと思います。
"Since big sister came all this way, I'd like to play a little game."
お、ゲーム？ゲーム！ここでね、ちょっと、ちょうど、これとこれがあるから、ちょっとゲームしたいと思って。よし！
"Oh, a game? A game! Right here, since we have this and that, I thought we could play a game. Alright!"
え、ということで、ルール説明してもいいかな？オッケー？
"So, is it okay if I explain the rules? Okay?"
オッケー！でね、おねえさんが描いた中、物とか何でもいいけど、なんか思い浮かぶんものをよふぃに行って、でもね
"Okay! So, whatever big sister drew, anything is fine, tell Yofi what comes to mind, but you know,"
あの、ヒント、ヒントとあの出してくれればいいかなと思って、よふぃが、あの、そのヒントを当てる。
"um, if you give me hints and stuff, that would be great, and I'll guess the hints."
いい？オッケーね？オッケー、オッケー！例えばね、そう、あの小さくてかわいいものとか、あれってなんだろ？なんだろ？って言ったら、あ、よふぃなの？って
"Good? Okay? Okay, okay! For example, right, something small and cute, like 'What could that be?', and I'm like, 'Ah, is it Yofi?'"
やっぱ小さくてかわいいじゃん。かわいい？うん、かわいいね。
"After all, she's small and cute. Cute? Yeah, cute."
でも、なんか、なんか思い浮かべたものあった？もうある？
"But um, did anything come to mind? Already have something?"
あー、なんか私的にはー、ねーさん的にはー、よく埋まってて可愛いー、熊かなって思ったんだけど。
"Ah, well, personally, from my perspective as the older sister, I thought it was a cute bear, all buried in there."
く、熊？く、は？そうなの？
"A- A bear? A... huh? Is that right?"
うちにもね、よくいるんだけどさ、あー動物？動物ベア？
"We have one of those too, you know... Ah, animal? Animal bear?"
ベア、そうなんだ。あのもうちょっと優しいものをお願いします。
"Bear, I see. Could you make it a bit more gentle, please?"
じゃあ私もね、私のマスコットでもあるんだけどー。
"Well, it's also my mascot..."
熊さんです！熊さんです！
"It's a bear! It's a bear!"
熊？熊？お、よくねパッとかいう、ぱっぱってよく言ってんだな。
"Bear? Bear? Oh, you often say things like 'pa' and 'pappa'."
え、そうなんです？どうなのよ、そんなの熊さん。よふぃちゃんが描いたらもう100%可愛いんじゃないかなと思ってちょっとその絵をね、おうちに飾りたいななんて思ってもけど。
"Huh, is that so? Really, a bear like that. Since Yofi-chan drew it, I thought it would be 100% cute, so I thought I'd like to decorate my house with that picture."
これ、これ飾る？これ飾る？あ、飾るー！
"Decorate this? Decorate this? Ah, decorate it!"
後でよ、これこれね、渡すもんじゃないよもう。後でね、ちゃんとね買って来るので今回はね
"Later, you know, this isn't something I'll hand over just like that. Later, I'll properly buy/bring it, so this time..."
ああ、ゲームやる、ゲーム、ゲームやりましょう。
"Ah, let's play a game, a game, let's play a game."
うん、オッケー！じゃ、一つのヒント、お願いします。
"Un, okay! Well, one hint, please."
何？一つ目のヒント。それはくまさん、くまさん。
"What? The first hint. It's a bear, a bear."
あ、くまさん？あ、それがヒントなの？
"Ah, a bear? Ah, is that the hint?"
そのまま！そのまま熊だと思ってた。
"As is! I thought it was just a bear."
え、そうなの？そうなの？え、始まってると思ってヒント全部言っちゃったよ！
"Eh, is that so? Is that so? Eh, I thought it had started and blurted out all the hints!"
あれがお楽しみだと思ってたー！
"I thought that was the fun part!"
じゃあ、もう一回、あの熊で、熊で、何？え、かわいくて。
"Well, then, once more, with that bear, with that bear, what? Eh, cute..."
かわいくて、じゃかわいいからもうラブラブしちゃおう。ラブラブしちゃって。
"Cute, well, since it's cute, let's get all lovey-dovey. Let's get all lovey-dovey."
うちのマスコットがあるんだけど。わかるかな？
"We have a mascot. Do you know?"
わかるよ！わかるよ！
"I know! I know!"
昔はよく埋まってたんだな、よふぃちゃんとぎゅってしてるえとか今度時間のとき。
"It used to be buried a lot, you know, pictures of Yofi-chan hugging it tightly, next time..."
あ、うん！描いてほしいな。描く描く！ねえ、じゃあそこと一緒に描くわ。やった！
"Ah, yeah! I want you to draw it. Draw, draw! Hey, then I'll draw it together with you. Yay!"
以上！あの、かわいい、かわいい顔がなんかもよもよしてる今。
"That's all! Um, the cute, cute face is all fuzzy right now."
うーん、どうしよう。よふぃちゃんが思うベアでいいよ。
"Hmm, what should I do? A bear that Yofi-chan thinks of is fine."
あ、よふぃが思う可愛い、かわいい熊でいい？
"Ah, is a cute, cute bear that Yofi thinks of okay?"
オッケー！これ熊かどうかわかんないんだけど。
"Okay! I don't know if this is a bear or not."
ここには熊で見える？
Can you see a bear here?
見える見える、え、見えるもん、熊、熊見える？
I can, I can! I can see it, a bear, can you see a bear?
これあんきもちゃんだよ？
This is Ankimo-chan, you know?
うん、わかるよ、かわいいよ！
Yeah, I get it, it's cute!
ほんと？ほんと？
Really? Really?
うんピンク、今ピンクなんだけど
Yeah, it's pink, it's pink right now though.
え、大丈夫？大丈夫？ピンク？
Eh, is it okay? Is it okay? Pink?
あんきもちゃんだからピンクにもなるものだから大丈夫！
Ankimo-chan can also turn pink, so it's fine!
ほんと？うちの、うん、うちの熊は何でもできるから大丈夫！
Really? Our, yeah, our bear can do anything, so it's fine!
そうなんだ。いい子だね、もう。
Is that so? What a good girl.
いや、ピちゃんの方が何倍もいい子よ。
No, Pi-chan is many times better.
え、呼び捨て？やばいな。
Eh, calling me by name? That's dangerous.
やばい、ピちゃんの場所ったらめっちゃん。え、よいピちゃんはもうきゅうとで、ビューティフルで
Oh no, Pi-chan's place is... Eh, Pi-chan is so cute and beautiful...
もう私の妹だから、うん、妹だから、いつでも一緒。
She's my younger sister, yeah, my younger sister, so we're always together.
ああ、ありがとう。嬉しいな。もう泣くじゃん、もう泣くよ。
Ah, thank you. I'm so happy. I'm gonna cry, I'm gonna cry.
あの、愛ちゃん、愛ちゃん、だめだ。かわいいね。あ、泣く。
Ah, Ai-chan, Ai-chan, no. How cute. Ah, crying.
うん、ありがとう。これで合ってるね、あんきもちゃん。うん、ピンクだけど、あ、ピンクだけど。
Yeah, thank you. Is this right, Ankimo-chan? Yeah, it's pink, but, ah, it's pink.
うん、ありがとう。ピンクで嬉しいよ、きっと。
Yeah, thank you. You must be happy it's pink.
よかった！嬉しいね。ありがとう、よかった、てってて。本当にありがとうね、さあ。
I'm glad! I'm so happy. Thank you, I'm so glad, te-te-te. Thank you so much, now.
あ、これで正解ね。改めて正解は
Ah, so this is correct. Once again, the correct answer is...
あん肝！やったー！あんきもちゃん、ありがとう！
Ankimo! Yay! Ankimo-chan, thank you!
あ、そっか、これが出るんだ。もうちょっと、あ、後で、後でちゃんと変えとく。ごめん、あんきもちゃん。
Ah, I see, this comes out. Wait a bit, ah, I'll change it properly later. Sorry, Ankimo-chan.
いや、いいよ、いいよ。ありがとう。かわいいね。
No, it's fine, it's fine. Thank you. So cute.
ありがとう！いいやり方だよ。飾り、これ？
Thank you! What a great way. Decorations, this?
うん、これ飾り、プレゼントでしょ？うん、うん、そうだけど、これ飾る。
Yeah, this decoration, it's a present, right? Yeah, yeah, that's right, display this.
そうだ。あ、ありがとう。あとで、あの、フレーム付きで送ってあげる。フレーム付きで。やったー！
I see. Ah, thank you. I'll send it with a frame later. With a frame. Yay!
ありがとう、お姉さん！ありがとう。次は、あの、一緒に行く、これ
Thank you, big sister! Thank you. Next, um, let's go together, this...
なんかやろうね！やろうね！楽しみにしてるよ。ありがとう！
Let's do something! Let's do it! I'm looking forward to it. Thank you!
あ、ラブゆねさん、ラブ、ラブ。みえる、あ、ラブゆねさん。
Ah, Lamy-ne-san, love, love. I can see, ah, Lamy-ne-san.
あ、ラブゆねさん。うわあ、ありがとう！
Ah, Lamy-ne-san. Wow, thank you!
本当におめでとう！ありがとう！お姉さんの愛が
Congratulations for real! Thank you! Big sister's love...
え、次いるのかな？次いるのかな？
Eh, is the next one here? Is the next one here?
よぺは、あのね、ラインガス、星川さんとオーランシー？
Yope, um, Reingas, Hoshikawa-san and Olandy?
え、外道路あんが？あ、だだんだんげん！
Eh, outside road? Ah, dadandangen!
ベスティ、ウェルカム！ここ、ぐだんよぺ。
Bestie, welcome! This is Gudan Yope.
いや、なんかぐだん。でもほら、もう疲れ。
No, kind of gudan. But look, I'm already tired.
なんか汚いよ、もう、申し訳ない。
It's kind of dirty, man, I'm sorry.
はろー、いらっしゃい！誰と、誰としゃべるの？誰と、誰と？
Hello, welcome! Who are you talking to? Who, who?
おけ、おけ。あ、じゃあ、じゃあ、じゃあ、みんな聞いて、そら。あ、ボボ？
Okay, okay. Ah, then, then, everyone listen, Sora. Ah, Bobo?
いや、ちょ、てばく。あ、ボボ、カナエルー！ここで、あー！
No, wait, tebaku. Ah, Bobo, Kanae-lu! Here, ah!
て、あるあ、誰？ゼータ。よぺ、ゼータ？ゼータフェスティア？フェスティアゼータ！
And, who? Zeta. Yope, Zeta? Zeta Vestia? Vestia Zeta!
フェスティアゼータの、わあ！わあ！そして、あるあ、あるあ、誰？
Vestia Zeta's, wow! Wow! And then, Alua, Alua, who?
クレイニさん？クレイニ？あ、クレイニ、クレイジー？
Kureni-san? Kureni? Ah, Kureni, Kureji?
あ、ありー！
Ah, Ari!
え、あれに？にい？あれに、あれにいる？いや、ダンリッシー、ダンリッシー、ダンリッシー？
Eh, Aleni? Nii? Aleni, is Aleni there? No, Danlissy, Danlissy, Danlissy?
かわいい！かわいい！3Dのおめでとう！
Cute! Cute! Congratulations on 3D!
プリティプリティ！かわいい、まあ、まあ、まあ、ありがとう！
Pretty pretty! Cute, well, well, well, thank you!
いや、かわいい！今、かわいいよ、みんな、みんなかわいい。もっとかわいい。
No, cute! Right now, it's cute, everyone, everyone is cute. Even cuter.
セイパイはなんか、お辞儀ちょっと、お辞儀ちょっとわかるでしょ、意味？意味？
Senpai, like, bowing a little, bowing a little, you know what I mean? Meaning?
そうだ。すっか、ほんと、たまに。すっか、ほんと、たまに。
That's right. Sometimes, really, sometimes. Sometimes, really, sometimes.
まあ、いいや。もう、私たちはゲームをやろうね、みんな。
Well, whatever. Let's play a game, everyone.
みんな、ルール説明したよ。ルールは、ほら、そうじゃん。
Everyone, I explained the rules. The rules, look, right.
でも、みんな、3人、これ、あれ。賢い、賢い、ってことか。
But, everyone, the three of you, this, that. Smart, clever, that means.
オッケー。な、から、ヒント、ヒント、これ、誰が一番しゃべる？
Okay. Now, from hints, hints, who's going to speak first?
誰？
Who?
私でいい？いい、いい、いい。私でいい？オッケー。
Is me okay? Good, good, good. Is me okay? Okay.
ヒント、第一、私からは...
Hint, first, from me...
ああ、やば、パワード、パワード、何？
Ah, oh no, powered, powered, what?
あ、ミス！は？まーにす？アーミス、アーミス！
Ah, miss! Huh? Maanisu? Aamisu, Aamisu!
アーミス、アーミス、くさい！アーミス、アーミス、どうしよう？
Aamisu, Aamisu, smelly! Aamisu, Aamisu, what should I do?
私、アーミスどうしよう？
Me drawing Aamisu, what should I do?
Ya, udahlah. Iya, amis, amis, gimana sih?
Yeah, whatever. Fishy, fishy, how does that work?
Ya, udahlah ya, emang bau sih.
Yeah, whatever, it really smells.
Iya, amis.
Yeah, fishy.
I, bau gitu. Jijik, imajinasi.
Ew, it smells like that. Gross, imagination.
Ya, oke, dah next lah, aduh, ini apa sih?
Yeah, okay, next. Oh, what is this?
Oke, hit dari Ollie, kalian.
Okay, a hint from Ollie, guys.
Nih.
Here.
Ini kalau lu sempat dengar, Ollie hanya ingin mengkonfirmasi exact, it's exactly what you think it is, oke?
If you happen to hear this, Ollie just wants to confirm exact—it's exactly what you think it is, okay?
Oli... chic... hah?
Oli... chic... Huh?
Oli apa? Oli...
Oli what? Oli...
Oli, licin, licin, licin.
Oli, slippery, slippery, slippery.
Licin!
Slippery!
Sial, harus banget itu.
Damn, it really has to be that.
Aduh, aku, aku takut, aku takut.
Aduh, I'm, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Bo, bo, bo, bo tambah ada bo sama yang kamu, tambah deh, apa deh, aku takut.
Bo, bo, bo, add bo and yours, add it, what is it, I'm scared.
Ini kalau lu masih belum bisa, kebangetan banget sih.
If you still can't get this, that's just too much.
Aduh!
Lu, nah, licin, urut akhir.
You, well, slippery, the last order.
Nih ya, tadi Ami sudah licin, sudah sekarang, heeh.
Here, earlier Ami was slippery, now, yeah.
Berkumis.
Mustached.
Waaah, licin berkumis.
Woah, slippery and mustached.
Kebayang enggak sih, licin berkumis, emang emang emang.
Can you imagine, slippery and mustached, really, really...
Iya, apa tuh? Emang, aku tahu.
Yeah, what is it? Really, I know.
Itu loh, bapak-bapak yang rasa...
That, you know, old men who taste...
Bapak-bapak habis pakai busa.
Old men after using foam.
Berkumis, emang, emang amis, amis berarti ikan kan? Ikan kan?
Mustached, really, really fishy, fishy means fish right? Fish right?
Hmm, apa ya?
Hmm, what is it?
Aduh, aduh, amis, bestie, amis, apa ya?
Aduh, aduh, fishy, bestie, fishy, what is it?
Oh, oke deh, oke deh, tapi, tapi...
Oh, okay then, okay then, but, but...
Oke, aku, aku boleh ngomong enggak? Licin, berkumis.
Okay, can I, can I speak? Slippery, mustached.
Berkumis.
Mustached.
Oli, yang ada oli, berkumoa.
Oli, the one with oli, mustach...
Berkumoa itu penting.
Mustachoa is important.
Lele! Bukan oli!
Catfish! Not oil!
Lele, lele, lele, lele. Benar, lele.
Catfish, catfish, catfish. Right, catfish.
Lele, itu jawabannya, lele.
Catfish, that's the answer, catfish.
Emang iya.
Is that so?
Enggak tahu. Lah, kok nanya balik sih?
I don't know. Huh, why are you asking back?
Enggak yakin. Yakin?
Not sure. Sure?
Udah yakin belum?
Are you sure yet?
Udah yakin. Ayo, cepat, apa?
Already sure. Come on, quick, what?
Ya udah.
Alright.
Hmm, coba yang benar adalah...
Hmm, let's see, the correct one is...
Tada! Lele! Lele! Lele!
Tada! Catfish! Catfish! Catfish!
Gimana, pintar banget kalian ini.
How's that, you guys are so smart.
Iya dong, aku, aku tadi sempat-sempat sempat kepikirannya anu yang coklat itu.
Of course, I, I earlier briefly thought of that brown one.
Anu, yang coklat, apa? Emang etap ya, lele, ada yang warna coklat ya.
Um, the brown one, what? Is it, catfish, there's a brown one, right.
Oh, iya iya iya iya. Iya iya iya iya. Aduh.
Oh, yeah yeah yeah yeah. Yeah yeah yeah yeah. Aduh.
Oke.
Okay.
Ya udah, tadi waktu dengar Ami saja, Oli dengarnya hah, ketek kah, gitu.
Alright, earlier when I heard just Ami, Oli heard huh, armpit, like that.
Tahu, ini, ini tak ketek gini.
You know, this, this is armpit like this.
Mana semua ketek itu, tenpay.
Where's all that armpit, tenpay.
Mohon maaf, kalau itu tolong jangan yang enggak-enggak ya.
Excuse me, please don't say weird things.
Ah, oke, oke.
Ah, okay, okay.
Punya Yopi, punya Yopi.
Yopi's, Yopi's.
Auw, oke, makasih besties.
Ouch, okay, thanks besties.
Ih, kok hayaku lucu banget deh.
Ew, why is Hayaku so cute.
Congrats ya, 3D-nya.
Congrats, on your 3D.
Ih, makasih, makasih sudah datang, alhamdulillah ya semuanya, semangat tahun meong-meong.
Ew, thanks, thanks for coming, thank God everyone, keep up the meow-meow spirit.
I love you, bye-bye, bye-bye.
Bye-bye cebol, apa lo juga cebol.
Bye-bye shorty, what, you're short too.
Ih, apa sih cebol bilang cebol, aduh capai.
Ugh, what is it, calling me shorty, man I'm tired.
Huh, aduh.
Hah, aduh.
Huh, sekalian ah.
Hah, let's check.
Iya, entar, mau undur dulu enggak? Kita-kita senam dulu ya, aduh capai, oke.
Yeah, wait, do you want to back off? Let's exercise first, man I'm tired, okay.
Hoo, hoo, hoo.
Ha, satu, dua, tiga, tiga, tiga, hayo.
Ha, one, two, three, three, three, come on.
Ha, loh, cebol, cebol.
Ha, look, shorty, shorty.
Yappi!
Aduh.
Apa sayang? Apa, kenapa sayang? Apa, kenapa sayang?
What, honey? What, why honey? What, why honey?
Bobo, bobo, bobo di sini.
Sleep, sleep, sleep here.
Aduh, gimana jadinya? Jadi tembu Natya?
Aduh, how does it end up? Becoming Natya's friend?
Udah keliling-keliling rumah.
Already went around the house.
Enggak ketemu piggy bank-nya Muna.
Couldn't find Muna's piggy bank.
Oh gitu.
Oh is that so.
Mau cari, mau cari di sini enggak?
Want to look, want to look here?
Ayo.
Come on.
Oya udah ayo cari.
Alright, let's look.
Tuh, di sini enggak ada, tuh, enggak ada.
Look, it's not here, look, it's not there.
Enggak ada, ih, enggak ada.
It's not there, ugh, it's not there.
Aduh, aduh, aduh, ada nih, ih.
Aduh, aduh, aduh, there's this, ugh.
Enggak ada, tuh, enggak ada.
It's not there, look, it's not there.
Tuh, enggak ada, mau ngapain?
Look, it's not there, what do you want to do?
Yah, enggak ada, tuh, cadangan kamu udah enggak ada di sini.
Ah, it's not there, look, your backup is not here.
Bosen.
Boring.
Yoh, ya udah, menjadi kamera aja deh, sana.
Yeah, alright, just become a camera, over there.
Oh iya, ya udah.
Yeah, alright.
Mana mau jadi kamera katanya? Ya udah, oke, dah.
Yeah, here, Muna is becoming a camera, she says, alright, okay, done.
Gimana, Beb?
How is it, Babe?
I, I was since I'm a cameraman right now.
I want to see everything that you got.
Oke, dari bawah.
Okay, from below.
Iya.
Yeah.
Woo!
Halo, dari bawah.
Hello, from below.
Hai.
Hi.
Koko jadi kameramen ternyata.
Turns out Koko became the cameraman.
Mah, mah.
Capek.
Tired.
Eh?
Gimana? Gimana? Kalau... kalau... Moona mau apa? Kalau kita... nyanyi?
How is it? If... if... what if Moona... sings?
Enggak mau.
No way.
Ayo dong! Aku tuh dari tadi enggak mau nyanyi!
Come on! I didn't want to sing this whole time!
Kenapa? Kenapa sih? Aku harusnya aku bikin Iou salon terus ngebotakin kamu di sini, tahu enggak?
Why? I should've made an Iou salon and shaved your head here!
Ya udah, ya udah, ya udah. Katanya Moona mau nyanyi.
Fine, fine. You said Moona wanted to sing.
I want to sing.
Sing what?
Apa ya? Bentar... Moona lupa mau nyanyi lagu apa?
What is it? Wait... Moona, what song did you want to sing?
Apa deh? Lagu-lagu lagu-lagu jadul... lagu lagu... itu loh yang gini!
Old-school songs... that one, like this!
Oh, yang gini! Yang gini!
Oh, like this! Like this!
Apaan? Ih, apa namanya? Moona lupa!
What? Ugh, what was it called? Moona forgot!
Sora... anu... na na na na na...
Sora... um... na na na na na...
Blue Bird!
Kita bilang 'senno' Blue Bird ya, oke? 'Senno' gitu, oke?
Let's say 'Senno' Blue Bird, okay? 'Senno' like that!
Senno... Blue Bird!
羽ばたいたら 戻らないと言って
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
目指したのは 蒼い 蒼い あの空
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
蒼い 蒼い あの空
That blue, blue sky
“悲しみ”はまだ覚えられず “切なさ”は今つかみはじめた
You've yet to learn sadness, now grasping pain
あなたへと抱く この感情も 今“言葉”に変わっていく
Even my feelings for you are turning into words
未知なる世界の 遊びから目覚めて この羽根を広げ 飛び立つ
Awakening from an unknown world, spread your wings and fly!
羽ばたいたら 戻らないと言って 目指したのは 白い 白い あの雲
If you could fly, seeking that white, white cloud
突き抜けていたら みつかると知って 振り切るほど 蒼い 蒼い あの空
Knowing you'll find it, to that blue, blue sky
蒼い 蒼い あの空
That blue, blue sky
愛想尽きたような音で 錆びれた古い窓は壊れた
That rusted, broken window shattered
見飽きたカゴはほら捨てていく 振り返ることはもうない
The cage you've grown sick of, no looking back
高鳴る鼓動に呼吸を共鳴させて この窓を蹴って 飛び立つ
With a racing heartbeat, share breath and take flight
駆け出したら 手にできると言って いざなうのは 遠い 遠い あの声
Once you run, you'll get what you need, called by a voice
眩しすぎた あなたの手も握って 求めるほど 蒼い 蒼い あの空
Holding your hand, the more I reach, that blue sky
誘うのは 遠い 遠い あの空
Calling to that far, far sky
外しすぎた あなたの手も握って 求めすぎて
Holding your hand too tight, asking for too much
求めるほど 遠い 遠い あの空
The more I yearn for that far, far sky
蒼い 蒼い あの空
That blue, blue sky
落ちていくとわかっていた それでも光を追い続けていく
Knowing I might fall, I'll still keep chasing that light
それでも 光を 追い続けていくよ
Still continuing to chase that light
羽ばたいたら 戻らないと言って 探したのは 白い 白い あの雲
If you could fly, what you searched for was that white cloud
突き抜けていたら みつかると知って 振り切るほど 蒼い 蒼い あの空
Knowing you'll find it, to that blue, blue sky
蒼い 蒼い あの空
That blue, blue sky
Ending ini kita kalau-kalau kan biasa...
Usually for endings like this, we...
Aduh... aduh... sakit.
Ow... ow... it hurts.
Capek. Aman?
Tired. You okay?
Enggak. Ternyata...
No. Turns out...
Yo, bukan drakor!
Yo, this isn't a K-drama!
Karena, karena kamu capek, Mona, ada rekomendasi nih.
Since you're tired, Mona, I've got a recommendation.
Iya, ambil, ambil, ambil.
Yeah, take it, take it, take it.
Guys, sorry, guys. Apa? Ada apa?
Guys, sorry, guys. What? What is it?
Ada apa?
What is it?
Ready?
Ready!
Wangi, wangi, wangi!
It smells so good, so good!
Ada bedak!
There's powder!
Sini, sini!
Over here, over here!
Udah, udah.
Enough, enough.
Keren, keren banget nih.
Cool, this is so cool.
Udah cepatin.
Hurry up and do it.
Ini tuh bukan dewa doran! Ini tuh...
This isn't Doraemon! This is...
Ini tuh kaya...
This is like...
Ini tuh kaya versi chaiya-chiaya, tapi terlalu canggih!
This is like the chaiya-chiaya version, but too advanced!
Udah, udah, udah, mendingan udah.
Enough, enough, better stop already.
Aman kan, ya? Aman. Makasih.
It's safe, right? Safe. Thanks.
Mona capek, Mona mau ke kamar, Mona ah.
Mona is tired, Mona wants to go to her room, ah.
Eh, bentar, bentar. Ada sesuatu. Bentar, kita mau kasih sesuatu, guys.
Eh, wait, wait. There's something. Wait, we want to give something, guys.
Oh, iya.
Oh, right.
Eh, besok ada apa? Kuku cial, kan ya? Kuku cial!
Eh, what's tomorrow? Cookial, right? Cookial!
Oke, 3, 2, 1, wayang!
Okay, 3, 2, 1, wayang!
Sebenarnya, gini banget.
Actually, it's really like this.
Iya, kok, kok, kok, dia inosens, sih?
Yeah, why, why, why is she so innocent?
Kayaknya, kayaknya. Risu, lu ngapain, sih?
It feels like... Risu, what are you doing?
3D Showcase Risu, September tanggal 18, besok!
Risu's 3D Showcase, September 18th, tomorrow!
Jamnya sama, guys.
The time is the same, guys.
Jam 8. Jam 8.
8 PM. 8 PM.
Jangan lupa ya, tonton. Tomorrow, yay! Jangan lupa ya.
Don't forget to watch, okay? Tomorrow, yay! Don't forget, okay?
Posenya.
The pose.
Posenya gimana tadi? Hah?
How was the pose earlier? Huh?
Sorosori, no senban ya.
Sorry-sorry, it's not the first time.
Udah, cape. Sumpah, Mona mau turun. Ya udah, thank you.
Enough, tired. Seriously, Mona wants to go down. Alright, thank you.
I love you, baby.
Bye, I love you, baby.
Tinggal sendirian, gimana ya?
Left alone, what should I do?
Sendirian aja, mah, ikka. Ya udah, mau keluar, kokeduru ya, guys. See you!
Being alone is fine, whatever. Alright, I'm going outside, Kokeduru, guys. See you!
Tiba-tiba, a pizza!
Suddenly, a pizza!
Terakhir nih, ya. Karena, ya, ihyu, iro, karena tuh, cool and response, gitu, mau...
Lastly, right. Because, yeah, ihyu, iro, because it's cool and response, like that, I want to...
Hai to omoimasu.
I think so...
So I want to try the what is it called again? Call and response, okay?
Jadi kalau Yopi bilang, Yopi, ya, kalian bisa, ya.
So if Yopi says, Yopi, yeah, you guys can do it, right?
Okey ya, ippatsu de ii yo ne? Ippatsu de ii? Okey? Ii yo ne? Okey?
Okay, right? Just once is fine, right? Just once is fine? Okay? Is that fine? Okay?
Kedo chotto ichido, okey? Yopi liyat lo, Yopi liyat ya.
But let's try it once, okay? Yopi, look, Yopi, look, yeah.
I'm I'm I'm safe, I'm seeing this all of this, okey?
I'm I'm I'm safe, I'm seeing all of this, okay?
We're gonna do it one, just one time, okay?
Ippatsu de iku yo? Ikeru? Okey?
We're going in one shot, okay? Can you? Okay?
Ja, Yopia! Yopia! Obeisah!
Now, Yopia! Yopia! Obeisah!
No, no. Okey? Okey?
No, no. Okay? Okay?
Wa!
Whoa!
Ee! Apa ya? Ini banyak banget, sebentar.
Eh! What is this? There's so many, wait.
Ini, ke mana ini? Eh?
Where are they going? Eh?
Nande, mana, mana? Ini depannya? Oh, shawa.
Why, where, where? Is this the front? Oh, shawa.
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Kori queen? Queen sorry.
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Kori queen? Queen sorry.
E! Hai, repository?
Eh! Hi, repository?
Tapi sa, ini sa, Yofuria no ai no katachi dakara, chotto chiisai na.
But you know, since this is Yofuria's shape of love, it's a bit small.
Yeri toka ya, ibaratnya cinta kalian ke Yopi, tapi kok kecil ya? Bisa lebih gede enggak? Bisa lebih gede enggak?
Like, metaphorically, your love for Yopi, but why is it small? Can it be bigger? Can it be bigger?
Oki dekiru? Motto Yofri no ai ni ai wo ne?
Can you make it bigger? More of Yofri's love into love, right?
Can you make it bigger the love? So this kind of like my love, because it's Yofuria's love for me, so can you make it bigger? Mhm.
Ima na obisah? Obisah? Obisah? Ah, okey.
Now na obisah? Obisah? Obisah? Ah, okay.
Doon! Are? Are? Oki, uwa!
Boom! Huh? Huh? Okay, whoa!
Ui! Barat, um... Oki na, Yopi bilang besar tapi enggak sebesar ini, maslaahnya.
Whew! Heavy, um... Big, Yopi said big, but not this big, that's the problem.
Gimana? Hai! Hahaha! Hai!
How is it? Hi! Hahaha! Hi!
Ki, ki, kyu...
Qu-, qu-, kyoo...
Ee! Kore wa okei do? Ah, ini ke? Ini ke? Motto misete! Hai!
Eh! Is this okay? Ah, is this it? Is this it? Show me more! Hi!
Mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, cintanya? Ui, giura!
Where, where, where, where, where is the love? Whew, giura!
Eh, bentar. Are? Are? E, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, cho, koi! Koi! Tasuete! Tasuete! Tasukete!
Eh, wait. Huh? Huh? Eh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, love! Love! Help me! Help me! Help me!
Yofuria! Yofuria! Yofuria! Ji, gomasu.
Yokoso! Halo, selamat datang. Ini kita udah ganti ya, hai. Aduh, cantik banget ya. Ah, kiri dan eh.
Welcome! Hello, welcome. We've changed now, hi. Oh, it's so pretty, yeah. Ah, left and eh.
Toyu koto wa, ano, kyo wa ano tsugi ryu ni natta no de, ano yaritai koto ga arimasu.
Which means, um, today since it became tsugi ryu, um, there is something I want to do.
So there is something I really, really want to do when I have this, um, tsugi ryu and this fingers.
So there is something I really, really want to do when I have this, um, tsugi ryu and these fingers.
Jadi dari kemarin Yopi pengen coba, kalau udah punya tangan, tangan dan body, dan body kayak gini, tentahu enggak?
So since yesterday Yopi wanted to try, if I already have hands, hands and body, and a body like this, do you know?
Masih ingat enggak? Masih ingat? Are you remember? Anoboter, anoboter, anoboter, anoboter.
Do you remember? Do you remember? Are you remember? Anoboter, anoboter, anoboter, anoboter.
Anoboter, itu iru? Iru? Ah, yokatta!
Anoboter, is it there? There? Ah, thank goodness!
Toyu koto de, yaritai no wa ne, shuwa, sign language, hello.
So what I want to do, um, is shuwa, sign language, hello.
Demo sa, ano shuwa mo ne, iroiro shurui ga atte, de, kyo wa ne, Nihongo to, etto, eigo no, ano American sign language wo yaritai to omoimasu.
But you know, um, sign language also has various types, and today, um, I want to do Japanese and, um, English, um, American sign language.
So, I'm going to do American sign language and a little bit of Japanese sign language. So, hi guys!
Thank you for coming here.
I really, really appreciate it. Thank you. Thank you.
Toyu koto de, hontoni arigatou, thank you. So, really, really, I love you all. I really love you all. Hi, I really love you all. Thank you for supporting me.
So, truly, thank you, thank you. So, really, really, I love you all. I really love you all. Hi, I really love you all. Thank you for supporting me.
Thank you. So, I am...
Let me introduce you again. Can can I introduce yourself? Ano jikoshouka ii? Ii, ii no? Ii no? Okey.
Let me introduce you again. Can can I introduce yourself? Um, is self-introduction okay? Is, is it okay? Is it okay? Okay.
Jikoshouka itte. So, thank you, my name is Iofi. Iofi is nice to meet you.
Let's do self-introduction. So, thank you, my name is Iofi. Iofi is nice to meet you.
So, I want to sing some language for you. Ah, I want to sing some song. Oh my god, I'm so nervous. (laughs) Toyu koto de, kyo wa ne, chotto shuwa de utaitai kyoku ga aru no.
So, I want to sing some language for you. Ah, I want to sing some song. Oh my god, I'm so nervous. (laughs) So today, um, I have a song I want to sing in sign language.
Mhm. Sorede ne, I want to sing something for you. So after this, please listen. Ii desu ka? Kiite kudasai. Boku ga kimi no mimi ni naru.
Mhm. And so, I want to sing something for you. So after this, please listen. Is that okay? Please listen. I will be your ears.
僕が君の耳になる
I will be your ears,
君のひとつになる
become a part of you.
そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I want to make such a dream come true right now.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる
I'll be your ears, I'll be your only one.
そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている
Even if you can't hear my voice, love echoes through.
そんな君をずっと 愛してる
I'll always be in love with you.
君が見ている景色 僕も見えるといいな
I wish I could experience what you see.
手と手重なり合って 君に夢中になった
Holding hand in hand made me crazy about you.
聞こえないことで僕らは 聞こえないことで二人を
By not being able to hear each other,
もっと知りたい 言葉にして
I want to know more about you, in words.
白黒(モノクロ)だった世界中が 鮮やかな色に変わった
The once-monochrome world is now colored wonderfully.
君が好きだよ どんな時も 溢れる想い奏でるよ
I love you, no matter what, playing with these overflowing feelings.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I'll be your ears, I'll be your only one, I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている
Love can echo through the air even though you can't hear my voice.
そんな君をずっと 愛してる
I'll always be in love with you.
君と見てきた景色 雨が降る日もあった
I've shared some rainy days with you.
瞳に映る涙の意味を 僕も知れるといいな
I wish I knew the meaning of your tears.
くだらないことで僕らは くだらないことで二人を 傷つけ合って
We hurt each other over silly things, over silly things,
本当ごめんね
I'm really sorry that I hurt you.
どんな風にすれば二人 いつまでも愛し愛されるままでいれるかな
How does a relationship between two people able to continue to love each other and last forever?
君がいるから頑張れるよ 支えてくれてありがとう
I'm able to continue because of you, thank you for supporting me.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I'll be your ears, I'll be your only one, I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている そんな君をずっと 愛してる
Love can echo through the air even though you can't hear my voice, I'll always be in love with you.
僕の手が枯れていくまで 君をまもり続けると誓うよ
I swear I'll keep you safe until my hands wither.
100年だって来世にだって いつまでも永遠に
Forever and ever, even after a century, or in the afterlife.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I'll be your ears, I'll be your only one, I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている そんな君をずっと 愛してる
Love can echo through the air even though you can't hear my voice, I'll always be in love with you.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる
I'll be your ears, I'll be your only one.
そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている そんな君と今
Love can echo through the air even though you can't hear my voice, even now, be with you.
僕が君の耳になる 君のひとりになる
I'll be your ears so that I can become a part of you.
そんな夢を今 叶えたい
I want to make such a dream come true right now.
声は聞こえなくても 愛が響いている そんな君をずっと 愛してる
Love can echo through the air even though you can't hear my voice, I'll always be in love with you.
いつだって君は嫌われ者だ
You're always someone who gets laughed at.
挙句に雨に降られ
Whatever you do, it never goes well in the end.
いつもどおり君は嫌われ者だ
You're someone who's been hated, without any reason even.
なにげなくとも遠ざけられて
People keep their distance from you.
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
If that's the case you should use my voice.
いつだって君は笑われ者だ
You're always the one who gets laughed at,
やることなすことついてなくて
with nothing you do ever going right,
挙句に雨に降られて
and ending up drenched in the rain.
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella flew away in the wind,
そこのノラはご苦労様と
and that stray cat over there acted so smug,
足を踏みつけてった
stepping all over you as always.
いつもどおり君は嫌われ者だ
Always as usual, you're disliked by everyone,
なんにもせずとも遠ざけられて
kept at a distance without doing anything wrong.
努力をしてみるけどその理由なんて「なんとなく？」で
Though you try your best, the reason is just "for no reason?"
君は途方にくれて悲しんでた
And you're left at a loss, feeling so sad.
ならあたしの使えばいいよ
If that's the case, you can just use my voice.
人によっては理解不能で
To some people, it's completely incomprehensible,
なんて耳障り ひどい声だって言われるけど
saying how harsh and jarring of a voice it is,
きっと君の力になれる
but I'm sure I can be of help to you.
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So try letting me sing.
そう君の 君だけの言葉で
Yes, with your words, and your words alone,
綴って 連ねて
stitch them together, string them along.
あたしがその思想を叫ぶから
Because I will shout out those thoughts of yours.
描いて 理想を
Paint your ideals,
その想いは誰にも触れさせない
and I won't let anyone touch those feelings.
ガラクタの声音はそして響く
And then the voice of the odds and ends resounds.
ありのままを不器用に繋いで
Clumsily connecting your true self,
目一杯大声を上げる
you raise your voice at the top of your lungs.
いつからか君は人気者だ
Before you knew it, you became popular;
たくさんの人に持て囃されて あたしも鼻が高い
you were idolized by so many, and I felt so proud too.
でもいつからか君は変わった
But somewhere along the way, you changed,
冷たくなって だけど寂しそうだった
becoming cold, yet looking so lonely.
「もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
"We've had enough of mechanical voices,"
僕は僕自身なんだよ」って
I am my own person," you said,
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって あたしを嫌った
until finally you couldn't hold it back and came to hate me.
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Someone says behind your back:
虎の威を借るキツネの癖に！
"Acting all tough using someone else's power!"
ねえ 君は一人で泣いてたんだね
Hey, you were crying all alone, weren't you?
聴こえる? この声
Can you hear this voice?
あたしがその謗りをかき消すから
I'll wipe away those slanders for you.
わかってる 本当は
I know, the truth is
君が誰より優しいってことを
that you're kinder than anyone else.
ガラクタの声音はそして歌った
And then the voice of the odds and ends sang on:
他の誰でもない君のために
for your sake, and no one else's.
軋んで 限界を超えて
Creaking, pushing past the limits,
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を思いついたことだろう
how many countless words we must have thought of.
だけど今は何一つ思いつかなくて
But now we can't think of a single one,
だけど何もかも分かった
yet we understood everything.
「そうか、きっとこれは夢だ。
"Oh right, surely this is a dream.
永遠に醒めない、君と会えた、そんな夢」
A dream where I met you, one that will never wake."
ガラクタは幸せそうな顔をした
The odds and ends wore a happy smile,
いくら呼んでももう動かない
no matter how much you called, it wouldn't move anymore.
泣いて叫んで 嘘だろ嘘だろって
Crying and shouting, "It's a lie, it's a lie!"
そんな気さき
with such frail hope.
ぼくを... 力尽きてガラクタが
Me... As the odds and ends ran out of strength,
一つだって動かしない
not a single part would move anymore.
想い出は涙にぽつりぽつりとその頬を濡らす
Memories drip as tears, wetting those cheeks one by one.
その時世界はその色を大きく変える
At that moment, the world drastically changes its colors,
悲しみと喜びとすべてを知った
knowing both sorrow and joy alike.
あたしの声はそして世界を再び駆け巡る
And once again, my voice travels across the world,
君のためにその声を大きく変える 悲しみと
changing its voice greatly for your sake, along with sorrow...
夜が明けて すべてを一人と一つはした
As dawn breaks, making everything one person and one entity.
言葉は歌になりこの世界を再び駆け巡る
Words become a song and once again run through this world.
君のためにその声を大きく変える
Changing that voice greatly for your sake.
石を落として今思い出が響く
Dropping a stone, now memories echo.
笑顔を見せてくれ 違って
Show me a smile, no, differently...
言葉は歌になりこの世界を再び駆け巡る
Words become a song and once again run through this world.
君のためにその声を大きく変える
Changing that voice greatly for your sake.
石を落として今思い出が響く
Dropping a stone, now memories echo.
想いが響く
Feelings echo through.
はあ…
Ah...
また会えた！
We meet again!
大丈夫？私は大丈夫。
Are you okay? I'm okay.
これ、続けていました。これいる。
I've been keeping this up. This is here.
また会えた！
We meet again!
というわけで、全部やっておきました。
So, I've gone ahead and done everything.
やっぱりだ！もう泣いちゃいたい、Yupiペンいん？
I knew it! I want to cry, but Yupi wants to...
あ、なんでビデオのこれしなぎさ…？
Oh, why is this seed crying?
So I want to just really really say thank you thank you thank you all for supporting me for... um, あ、でももうすぐ3年ですよね？
So, I want to just really, really say thank you, thank you, thank you all for supporting me for... um, I think it's almost 3 years, right?
もうすぐ3年です。Thank you、makasih untuk semua support, untuk semua oshi, untuk...
It's almost 3 years. Thank you, makasih untuk semua support, untuk semua oshi, untuk...
mendorong Yupi selama 3 tahun, hampir 3 tahun ya, hampir 3 tahun.
3年、本当にありがとうございます！
3 years, thank you so much!
えっと、マネージャーさんもマネージャー泣いてる？今泣いてる？え、泣かないで形や！
Manager-san, are you crying? Don't cry, okay!
マネージャーさん、ありがとうございます！あの、本当にみなさん、Hololive Indonesiaの全体のみなさん、ありがとうございます！
Manager-san, thank you! And thank you to everyone in Hololive Indonesia!
本当に仲良くしてくれてありがとうございます！Holostarsのみんなもありがとうございます！
Thank you for getting along with me! And thank you to Holostars too!
イオフィをHololive Indonesia一期生として受け入れてくれてありがとうございます！あの、Yagoo大好きだよ！
Thank you for welcoming Iofi as a Hololive Indonesia 1st Gen! And Yagoo, I love you!
うん、なんか言ってもだけど、あいつ好きだよ！マカシワ！
I mean, whatever you say, I love him! Thank you!
Okay、じゃあリハーサルにきた最後だから、歌最後の、だから...
Okay, so this rehearsal is going to be the very last song, so...
だ準備？これは bakal jadi call and response terakhir, oke?
Are you ready? This will be the last call and response, okay?
本当に今日ありがとうございます！じゃ...
Thank you so much today! Now...
最後の曲いきたいと思います。聞いてください。
I would like to go to the final song. Please listen.
可愛い！
Cute!
予想外 question 想定外 answer
Unexpected question, unforeseen answer,
clap your hands
give me love , give me love
give me love, give me love,
need your love , more i need your love
need your love, more I need your love,
let me know , if you love me
let me know, if you love me,
i 'll move on , with all my love
I'll move on, with all my love.
恋し ちゃう かも
Might fall in love
鮮やかな セカイ に
in a vibrant world.
好きっていい でしょ
Is it okay to like it?
私 色 に 染まる
Coloring it in my own hue.
ちちょい の ちょい でしょ
It's a breeze, right?
悪戯な プリンセス って 笑顔 で
Smiling like a mischievous princess.
本気 出し ちゃう もん
I'll show you I mean it,
同じ 想い が いい な
hoping you feel the same way.
いつだって 近く に いたいの
I want to be close to you always,
でも 待っている だけなんて 嫌よ 、 つまらない
but just waiting around is boring.
変わらない 宝物 宇宙 で 一番
An unchanging treasure, the best in the universe.
想いし ちゃう よう に
Just as I yearn for you,
歌いし ちゃう よう に
just as I sing for you,
描いし ちゃえば 私らしさ
painting it makes it uniquely me.
夢見し ちゃう よう な
Like dreaming away,
願いし ちゃう よう な
like wishing away,
期待し ちゃう 未来 開く の
opening up a future filled with hope.
困りし ちゃう くらい に
To the point of embarrassment,
踊りし ちゃう くらい に
to the point of dancing,
笑って ほしい そう キミ だ から
I want you to smile, because it's you.
分かりし ちゃう よう な
Like understanding you,
似合し ちゃう よう な
like suiting you,
イメージ し ちゃう question
imagining a question (& answer).
じゃ 違う の
But wait, that's wrong!
大好きだ もん そう
Because I love you so much,
何 度 だって 言う よ
I'll say it as many times as it takes.
もう 運命 かな 見ていて ほしい の
Is this destiny? I want you to watch over me.
live it up , get it up ,
live it up, get it up,
hands up , pick me up ,
hands up, pick me up,
take you up , jump up ,
take you up, jump up,
shouting up , dance up
shouting up, dance up.
気付いし ちゃう みたい
As if realizing it,
分かりし ちゃう みたい
as if understanding it,
飛び込み じゃお もっと 楽しん じゃお ほら
dive right in and enjoy it even more.
想いし ちゃう よう に
Just as I yearn for you,
歌いし ちゃう よう に
just as I sing for you,
描いし ちゃえば 私らしさ
painting it makes it uniquely me.
夢見し ちゃう よう な
Like dreaming away,
願いし ちゃう よう な
like wishing away,
期待し ちゃう 未来 開く の
opening up a future filled with hope.
困りし ちゃう くらい に
To the point of embarrassment,
踊りし ちゃう くらい に
to the point of dancing,
笑って ほしい そう キミ だ から
I want you to smile, because it's you.
分かりし ちゃう よう な
Like understanding you,
似合し ちゃう よう な
like suiting you,
イメージ し ちゃう question
imagining a question (& answer).
じゃ 違う の
But wait, that's wrong!
キミ の 一番 に なる の
I'm going to become your number one!
give me love , give me love
give me love, give me love,
need your love , more i need your love
need your love, more I need your love,
let me know , if you love me
let me know, if you love me,
i 'll move on , with all my love
I'll move on, with all my love,
give me love , give me love
give me love, give me love,
need your love , more i need your love
need your love, more I need your love,
let me know , if you love me
let me know, if you love me,
i 'll move on , with all my love
I'll move on, with all my love,
give me love , give me love
give me love, give me love.
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more,
more, more, more, more!
飛び込んじゃいもっと！
Dive in even more!
新しいジャポニカ ほら ほら ほら
A brand new Japonica, hey, hey, hey!
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more,
飛び込んじゃえば 私らしさ
If I dive in, it's just so me!
新しい未来 フリーダムの
A brand new future, full of freedom,
もっと もっと 泣いて 笑ってほしい
I want you to cry and smile even more,
君だから わかっちゃうよな
Because it's you, I can understand.
出会っちゃうような イメージじゃおさまんない
An encounter that defies all imagination!
Give me love, give me love, 24/7, we all my more
Give me love, give me love